35 millimeter slides
Marist Archives and Special Collections
- 35 millimeter slides, 2.1.5.1
  - Carousel number 13 [Christmas; West Point football game; wedding; golf; Hawaii; Lowell and Frances Thomas; Lowell Thomas and unidentified man (circa 1950s); unidentified people and places], circa 1950s, circa 1970s; 19 (Box 1585)
    - [Carousel number 13 [Christmas; West Point football game; wedding; golf; Hawaii; Lowell and Frances Thomas; Lowell Thomas and unidentified man (circa 1950s); unidentified people and places]: People sitting at a dining table], 11
    - [Carousel number 13 [Christmas; West Point football game; wedding; golf; Hawaii; Lowell and Frances Thomas; Lowell Thomas and unidentified man (circa 1950s); unidentified people and places]: Two men by a fire pit], 12
    - [Carousel number 13 [Christmas; West Point football game; wedding; golf; Hawaii; Lowell and Frances Thomas; Lowell Thomas and unidentified man (circa 1950s); unidentified people and places]: View from an airplane window], 13
    - [Carousel number 13 [Christmas; West Point football game; wedding; golf; Hawaii; Lowell and Frances Thomas; Lowell Thomas and unidentified man (circa 1950s); unidentified people and places]: View from an airplane window], 14
    - [Carousel number 13 [Christmas; West Point football game; wedding; golf; Hawaii; Lowell and Frances Thomas; Lowell Thomas and unidentified man (circa 1950s); unidentified people and places]: View from an airplane window], 15
    - [Carousel number 13 [Christmas; West Point football game; wedding; golf; Hawaii; Lowell and Frances Thomas; Lowell Thomas and unidentified man (circa 1950s); unidentified people and places]: Street running by football stadium], 16
    - [Carousel number 13 [Christmas; West Point football game; wedding; golf; Hawaii; Lowell and Frances Thomas; Lowell Thomas and unidentified man (circa 1950s); unidentified people and places]: Frances Ryan Thomas sitting on balcony, looking at water], 17
    - [Carousel number 13 [Christmas; West Point football game; wedding; golf; Hawaii; Lowell and Frances Thomas; Lowell Thomas and unidentified man (circa 1950s); unidentified people and places]: People at table], 18
    - [Carousel number 13 [Christmas; West Point football game; wedding; golf; Hawaii; Lowell and Frances Thomas; Lowell Thomas and unidentified man (circa 1950s); unidentified people and places]: Street], 19
    - [Carousel number 13 [Christmas; West Point football game; wedding; golf; Hawaii; Lowell and Frances Thomas; Lowell Thomas and unidentified man (circa 1950s); unidentified people and places]: Frances Ryan Thomas sitting at a table with two other women], 20
    - [Carousel number 13 [Christmas; West Point football game; wedding; golf; Hawaii; Lowell and Frances Thomas; Lowell Thomas and unidentified man (circa 1950s); unidentified people and places]: Frances Ryan Thomas sitting on balcony with Lowell Thomas, looking at water], 21
    - [Carousel number 13 [Christmas; West Point football game; wedding; golf; Hawaii; Lowell and Frances Thomas; Lowell Thomas and unidentified man (circa 1950s); unidentified people and places]: Frances Ryan Thomas sitting on balcony with Lowell Thomas, looking at water], 22
  - Carousel number 14 [Lowell Thomas broadcasts from a hospital; graduation; Florida], circa 1960s - 1970s; 20 (Box 1585)
    - Beginning of Carousel number 14 [Lowell Thomas broadcasts from a hospital; graduation; Florida] [: Man waterskiing], 1
    - [Carousel number 14 [Lowell Thomas broadcasts from a hospital; graduation; Florida]: Man waterskiing on lake], 2
    - [Carousel number 14 [Lowell Thomas broadcasts from a hospital; graduation; Florida]: Man waterskiing], 3
    - [Carousel number 14 [Lowell Thomas broadcasts from a hospital; graduation; Florida]: Man waterskiing], 4
    - [Carousel number 14 [Lowell Thomas broadcasts from a hospital; graduation; Florida]: Lake, boat in the distance], 5
    - [Carousel number 14 [Lowell Thomas broadcasts from a hospital; graduation; Florida]: Nurse standing with Lowell Thomas], 6
    - [Carousel number 14 [Lowell Thomas broadcasts from a hospital; graduation; Florida]: Lowell Thomas sitting at a table, broadcasting at a hospital], 7
    - [Carousel number 14 [Lowell Thomas broadcasts from a hospital; graduation; Florida]: Lowell Thomas sitting at a table, broadcasting at a hospital], 8
    - [Carousel number 14 [Lowell Thomas broadcasts from a hospital; graduation; Florida]: Lowell Thomas sitting at a table, broadcasting at a hospital], 9
    - [Carousel number 14 [Lowell Thomas broadcasts from a hospital; graduation; Florida]: Broadcasting equipment], 10
    - [Carousel number 14 [Lowell Thomas broadcasts from a hospital; graduation; Florida]: Nurse standing by table Lowell Thomas was broadcasting at], 11
    - [Carousel number 14 [Lowell Thomas broadcasts from a hospital; graduation; Florida]: Broadcasting equipment], 12
    - [Carousel number 14 [Lowell Thomas broadcasts from a hospital; graduation; Florida]: Sign for building that says "Walt Disney World Preview Center"], 13
    - [Carousel number 14 [Lowell Thomas broadcasts from a hospital; graduation; Florida]: Sign that says "Lion Country Safari"], 14
    - [Carousel number 14 [Lowell Thomas broadcasts from a hospital; graduation; Florida]: People wearing graduation caps and gowns], 15
    - [Carousel number 14 [Lowell Thomas broadcasts from a hospital; graduation; Florida]: Lowell Thomas broadcasting from a hospital], 16
    - [Carousel number 14 [Lowell Thomas broadcasts from a hospital; graduation; Florida]: Sign (illegible)], 17
    - [Carousel number 14 [Lowell Thomas broadcasts from a hospital; graduation; Florida]: Graduation ceremony], 18
    - [Carousel number 14 [Lowell Thomas broadcasts from a hospital; graduation; Florida]: Graduation ceremony], 19
    - [Carousel number 14 [Lowell Thomas broadcasts from a hospital; graduation; Florida]: Graduation ceremony], 20
  Box 1586
- 35 millimeter slides, 2.1.5.1
  - Carousel number 14 (continued from previous box) [Lowell Thomas broadcasts from a hospital; graduation; Florida], circa 1960s - 1970s; 1 (Box 1586)
    - [Carousel number 14 (continued from previous box) [Lowell Thomas broadcasts from a hospital; graduation; Florida]: Person waterskiing], 1
    - [Carousel number 14 (continued from previous box) [Lowell Thomas broadcasts from a hospital; graduation; Florida]: People waterskiing], 2
    - [Carousel number 14 (continued from previous box) [Lowell Thomas broadcasts from a hospital; graduation; Florida]: Man waterskiing], 3
    - [Carousel number 14 (continued from previous box) [Lowell Thomas broadcasts from a hospital; graduation; Florida]: Two women standing on beach], 4
    - [Carousel number 14 (continued from previous box) [Lowell Thomas broadcasts from a hospital; graduation; Florida]: Beach], 5
    - [Carousel number 14 (continued from previous box) [Lowell Thomas broadcasts from a hospital; graduation; Florida]: Lake], 6
    - [Carousel number 14 (continued from previous box) [Lowell Thomas broadcasts from a hospital; graduation; Florida]: Lowell Thomas and another man wearing hardhats in front of building being constructed], 7
    - [Carousel number 14 (continued from previous box) [Lowell Thomas broadcasts from a hospital; graduation; Florida]: Two women playing cards at a table], 8
    - [Carousel number 14 (continued from previous box) [Lowell Thomas broadcasts from a hospital; graduation; Florida]: Two women playing cards at a table], 9
    - [Carousel number 14 (continued from previous box) [Lowell Thomas broadcasts from a hospital; graduation; Florida]: Lowell Thomas giving a broadcast, sitting with a boy. LT's dog sitting on table ], 10
    - [Carousel number 14 (continued from previous box) [Lowell Thomas broadcasts from a hospital; graduation; Florida]: Lowell Thomas giving a broadcast, sitting with a boy. LT's dog on table ], 11
    - [Carousel number 14 (continued from previous box) [Lowell Thomas broadcasts from a hospital; graduation; Florida]: Construction site], 12
    - [Carousel number 14 (continued from previous box) [Lowell Thomas broadcasts from a hospital; graduation; Florida]: Lowell Thomas giving a broadcast, sitting with a boy. LT's dog on table ], 13
    - [Carousel number 14 (continued from previous box) [Lowell Thomas broadcasts from a hospital; graduation; Florida]: Lowell Thomas giving a broadcast, sitting with a boy. LT's dog on table ], 14
    - [Carousel number 14 (continued from previous box) [Lowell Thomas broadcasts from a hospital; graduation; Florida]: Lowell Thomas giving a broadcast, sitting with a boy. LT's dog on table ], 15
    - [Carousel number 14 (continued from previous box) [Lowell Thomas broadcasts from a hospital; graduation; Florida]: Lowell Thomas's dog sitting in golf cart], 16
    - [Carousel number 14 (continued from previous box) [Lowell Thomas broadcasts from a hospital; graduation; Florida]: Lowell Thomas giving a broadcast, sitting with a boy. LT's dog on table ], 17
    - [Carousel number 14 (continued from previous box) [Lowell Thomas broadcasts from a hospital; graduation; Florida]: Lowell Thomas giving a broadcast, sitting with a boy. LT's dog on table ], 18
    - [Carousel number 14 (continued from previous box) [Lowell Thomas broadcasts from a hospital; graduation; Florida]: Lowell Thomas's dog sitting in golf cart], 19
    - [Carousel number 14 (continued from previous box) [Lowell Thomas broadcasts from a hospital; graduation; Florida]: Benches on grass], 20
  - Carousel number 14 (continued from previous box) [Lowell Thomas broadcasts from a hospital; graduation; Florida] [Items 1-13] Carousel number 15 [Items 14-20], circa 1960s - 1970s; 2 (Box 1586)
    - [Carousel number 14 (continued from previous box) [Lowell Thomas broadcasts from a hospital; graduation; Florida]: Road and trees], 1
    - [Carousel number 14 (continued from previous box) [Lowell Thomas broadcasts from a hospital; graduation; Florida]: Woman standing by a fence], 2
    - [Carousel number 14 (continued from previous box) [Lowell Thomas broadcasts from a hospital; graduation; Florida]: Wooden archway], 3
    - [Carousel number 14 (continued from previous box) [Lowell Thomas broadcasts from a hospital; graduation; Florida]: Road lined with trees], 4
    - [Carousel number 14 (continued from previous box) [Lowell Thomas broadcasts from a hospital; graduation; Florida]: Man and woman together], 5
    - [Carousel number 14 (continued from previous box) [Lowell Thomas broadcasts from a hospital; graduation; Florida]: Man riding small tractor with a cart attached. Boy sitting in cart], 6
    - [Carousel number 14 (continued from previous box) [Lowell Thomas broadcasts from a hospital; graduation; Florida]: Two men and a woman standing inside house], 7
    - [Carousel number 14 (continued from previous box) [Lowell Thomas broadcasts from a hospital; graduation; Florida]: Two men and woman standing outside of house], 8
    - [Carousel number 14 (continued from previous box) [Lowell Thomas broadcasts from a hospital; graduation; Florida]: Beach], 9
    - [Carousel number 14 (continued from previous box) [Lowell Thomas broadcasts from a hospital; graduation; Florida]: Baby lying on towel], 10
    - [Carousel number 14 (continued from previous box) [Lowell Thomas broadcasts from a hospital; graduation; Florida]: Lowell Thomas with broadcasting equipment, festival ahead of him], 11
    - [Carousel number 14 (continued from previous box) [Lowell Thomas broadcasts from a hospital; graduation; Florida]: Ostriches crossing the road], 12
    - [Carousel number 14 (continued from previous box) [Lowell Thomas broadcasts from a hospital; graduation; Florida]: Lake], 13
    - Beginning of Carousel number 15 [Lowell and Frances Thomas; skiing; miscellaneous] [:Lowell Thomas and his dog in golf cart], 14
    - [Carousel number 15 [Lowell and Frances Thomas; skiing; miscellaneous]: Lowell Thomas and his dog in golf cart], 15
    - [Carousel number 15 [Lowell and Frances Thomas; skiing; miscellaneous]: Lowell Thomas and his dog in golf cart], 16
    - [Carousel number 15 [Lowell and Frances Thomas; skiing; miscellaneous]: Lowell Thomas and his dog in golf cart], 17
    - [Carousel number 15 [Lowell and Frances Thomas; skiing; miscellaneous]: Lowell Thomas and his dog in golf cart], 18
    - [Carousel number 15 [Lowell and Frances Thomas; skiing; miscellaneous]: Lowell Thomas sitting in golf cart], 19
    - [Carousel number 15 [Lowell and Frances Thomas; skiing; miscellaneous]: Lowell Thomas and his dog in golf cart], 20
  - Carousel number 15 [Lowell and Frances Thomas; skiing; miscellaneous], circa late 1960s - 1970s; 3 (Box 1586)
    - [Carousel number 15 [Lowell and Frances Thomas; skiing; miscellaneous]: Lowell Thomas with his dog in golf cart], 1
    - [Carousel number 15 [Lowell and Frances Thomas; skiing; miscellaneous]: Lowell Thomas in golf cart], 2
    - [Carousel number 15 [Lowell and Frances Thomas; skiing; miscellaneous]: Lowell Thomas in golf cart], 3
    - [Carousel number 15 [Lowell and Frances Thomas; skiing; miscellaneous]: Lowell Thomas in golf cart], 4
    - [Carousel number 15 [Lowell and Frances Thomas; skiing; miscellaneous]: Lowell Thomas sitting in chair, reading papers], 5
    - [Carousel number 15 [Lowell and Frances Thomas; skiing; miscellaneous]: Lowell Thomas sitting at desk, writing], 6
    - [Carousel number 15 [Lowell and Frances Thomas; skiing; miscellaneous]: Lowell Thomas giving a broadcast], 7
    - [Carousel number 15 [Lowell and Frances Thomas; skiing; miscellaneous]: Lowell Thomas giving a broadcast], 8
    - [Carousel number 15 [Lowell and Frances Thomas; skiing; miscellaneous]: Lowell Thomas sitting in chair], 9
    - [Carousel number 15 [Lowell and Frances Thomas; skiing; miscellaneous]: Lowell Thomas leaning against tree], 10
    - [Carousel number 15 [Lowell and Frances Thomas; skiing; miscellaneous]: Lowell Thomas giving a broadcast], 11
    - [Carousel number 15 [Lowell and Frances Thomas; skiing; miscellaneous]: Lowell Thomas sitting on fence, near garage], 12
    - [Carousel number 15 [Lowell and Frances Thomas; skiing; miscellaneous]: Lowell Thomas sitting on fence, near garage], 13
    - [Carousel number 15 [Lowell and Frances Thomas; skiing; miscellaneous]: Lowell Thomas standing in front of model planes], 14
    - [Carousel number 15 [Lowell and Frances Thomas; skiing; miscellaneous]: Lowell Thomas sitting at table, reading back of book], 15
    - [Carousel number 15 [Lowell and Frances Thomas; skiing; miscellaneous]: Lowell Thomas walking down stairs, reading a book], 16
    - [Carousel number 15 [Lowell and Frances Thomas; skiing; miscellaneous]: People walking into building], 17
    - [Carousel number 15 [Lowell and Frances Thomas; skiing; miscellaneous]: Lowell Thomas sitting in golf cart], 18
    - [Carousel number 15 [Lowell and Frances Thomas; skiing; miscellaneous]: Lowell Thomas sitting in golf cart], 19
    - [Carousel number 15 [Lowell and Frances Thomas; skiing; miscellaneous]: Lowell Thomas, Frances Ryan Thomas, and another woman sitting on stone ledge], 20
  - Carousel number 15 [Lowell and Frances Thomas; skiing; miscellaneous, circa late 1960s - 1970s; 4 (Box 1586)
    - [Carousel number 15 [Lowell and Frances Thomas; skiing; miscellaneous]: Frances Ryan Thomas waiting to board a bus], 1
    - [Carousel number 15 [Lowell and Frances Thomas; skiing; miscellaneous]: Man and three girls standing in a driveway], 2
    - [Carousel number 15 [Lowell and Frances Thomas; skiing; miscellaneous]: Frances Ryan Thomas sitting on a boat], 3
    - [Carousel number 15 [Lowell and Frances Thomas; skiing; miscellaneous]: Deck and boats on water], 4
    - [Carousel number 15 [Lowell and Frances Thomas; skiing; miscellaneous]: Woman sitting on boat], 5
    - [Carousel number 15 [Lowell and Frances Thomas; skiing; miscellaneous]: Woman sitting on boat], 6
    - [Carousel number 15 [Lowell and Frances Thomas; skiing; miscellaneous]: Lowell Thomas sitting at a booth with Frances Ryan Thomas], 7
    - [Carousel number 15 [Lowell and Frances Thomas; skiing; miscellaneous]: Lowell Thomas and Frances Ryan Thomas on a boat], 8
    - [Carousel number 15 [Lowell and Frances Thomas; skiing; miscellaneous]: Woman sitting at boat controls], 9
    - [Carousel number 15 [Lowell and Frances Thomas; skiing; miscellaneous]: Lowell Thomas giving a broadcast], 10
    - [Carousel number 15 [Lowell and Frances Thomas; skiing; miscellaneous]: Lowell Thomas giving a broadcast], 11
    - [Carousel number 15 [Lowell and Frances Thomas; skiing; miscellaneous]: Lowell Thomas giving a broadcast], 12
    - [Carousel number 15 [Lowell and Frances Thomas; skiing; miscellaneous]: Lowell Thomas and Frances Ryan Thomas sitting in a pew], 13
    - [Carousel number 15 [Lowell and Frances Thomas; skiing; miscellaneous]: Frances Ryan Thomas lying on a couch], 14
    - [Carousel number 15 [Lowell and Frances Thomas; skiing; miscellaneous]: Man skiing], 15
    - [Carousel number 15 [Lowell and Frances Thomas; skiing; miscellaneous]: Lowell Thomas with three other people on skiis], 16
    - [Carousel number 15 [Lowell and Frances Thomas; skiing; miscellaneous]: Lowell Thomas skiing], 17
    - [Carousel number 15 [Lowell and Frances Thomas; skiing; miscellaneous]: Lowell Thomas and three other people on skiis], 18
    - [Carousel number 15 [Lowell and Frances Thomas; skiing; miscellaneous]: Lowell Thomas with two other men on skiis], 19
    - [Carousel number 15 [Lowell and Frances Thomas; skiing; miscellaneous]: Lowell Thomas and two other people on skiis], 20
  - Carousel number 15 [Lowell and Frances Thomas; skiing; miscellaneous, circa late 1960s - 1970s; 5 (Box 1586)
    - [Carousel number 15 [Lowell and Frances Thomas; skiing; miscellaneous]: Note to Lowell Thomas from Teddy Kolek], 1
    - [Carousel number 15 [Lowell and Frances Thomas; skiing; miscellaneous]: Note to Lowell Thomas from Teddy Kolek], 2
    - [Carousel number 15 [Lowell and Frances Thomas; skiing; miscellaneous]: Note to Lowell Thomas from Teddy Kolek], 3
    - [Carousel number 15 [Lowell and Frances Thomas; skiing; miscellaneous]: Note to Lowell Thomas from Teddy Kolek], 4
    - [Carousel number 15 [Lowell and Frances Thomas; skiing; miscellaneous]: Note to Lowell Thomas from Teddy Kolek], 5
    - [Carousel number 15 [Lowell and Frances Thomas; skiing; miscellaneous]: Note to Lowell Thomas from Teddy Kolek], 6
    - [Carousel number 15 [Lowell and Frances Thomas; skiing; miscellaneous]: Hollowed out tree], 7
    - [Carousel number 15 [Lowell and Frances Thomas; skiing; miscellaneous]: Large building in the distance, Mountains in the background], 8
    - [Carousel number 15 [Lowell and Frances Thomas; skiing; miscellaneous]: Man wearing a United States Airlines jacket], 9
    - [Carousel number 15 [Lowell and Frances Thomas; skiing; miscellaneous]: Little girl holding cookie], 10
    - [Carousel number 15 [Lowell and Frances Thomas; skiing; miscellaneous]: Water running through canyon], 11
    - [Carousel number 15 [Lowell and Frances Thomas; skiing; miscellaneous]: Woman standing behind desk], 12
    - [Carousel number 15 [Lowell and Frances Thomas; skiing; miscellaneous]: Sign that reads "The ZCMI Center"], 13
    - [Carousel number 15 [Lowell and Frances Thomas; skiing; miscellaneous]: Aerial view of mountains], 14
    - [Carousel number 15 [Lowell and Frances Thomas; skiing; miscellaneous]: City building], 15
    - [Carousel number 15 [Lowell and Frances Thomas; skiing; miscellaneous]: Bus that says "Eat Out Often"], 16
    - [Carousel number 15 [Lowell and Frances Thomas; skiing; miscellaneous]: Vast land], 17
    - [Carousel number 15 [Lowell and Frances Thomas; skiing; miscellaneous]: A window], 18
    - [Carousel number 15 [Lowell and Frances Thomas; skiing; miscellaneous]: Looking out from a window, people riding by on horses], 19
    - [Carousel number 15 [Lowell and Frances Thomas; skiing; miscellaneous]: Field], 20
  - Carousel number 15 [Lowell and Frances Thomas; skiing; miscellaneous [Items 1-6] Carousel number 16 [Items 7-, circa late 1960s - 1970s; 6 (Box 1586)
    - [Carousel number 15 [Lowell and Frances Thomas; skiing; miscellaneous]: Washed-out photo], 1
    - [Carousel number 15 [Lowell and Frances Thomas; skiing; miscellaneous]: Washed-out photo], 2
    - [Carousel number 15 [Lowell and Frances Thomas; skiing; miscellaneous]: Looking out from a window, people riding by on horses], 3
    - [Carousel number 15 [Lowell and Frances Thomas; skiing; miscellaneous]: Dark photo], 4
    - [Carousel number 15 [Lowell and Frances Thomas; skiing; miscellaneous]: Dark photo], 5
    - [Carousel number 15 [Lowell and Frances Thomas; skiing; miscellaneous]: Sign that reads "The Church of Ireland. Parish Church of St. Stephen"], 6
    - Beginning of Carousel number 16 [Europe; commercially purchased slides of Europe] [: Aerial view of land, mountains], 7
    - [Carousel number 16 [Europe; commercially purchased slides of Europe]: Aerial view of city], 8
    - [Carousel number 16 [Europe; commercially purchased slides of Europe]: Aerial view of mountains], 9
    - [Carousel number 16 [Europe; commercially purchased slides of Europe]: Aerial view of mountains], 10
    - [Carousel number 16 [Europe; commercially purchased slides of Europe]: View of body of water], 11
    - [Carousel number 16 [Europe; commercially purchased slides of Europe]: Aerial view of land], 12
    - [Carousel number 16 [Europe; commercially purchased slides of Europe]: Jet taking off], 13
    - [Carousel number 16 [Europe; commercially purchased slides of Europe]: On runway, jet engine], 14
    - [Carousel number 16 [Europe; commercially purchased slides of Europe]: On runway, jet engine], 15
    - [Carousel number 16 [Europe; commercially purchased slides of Europe]: Man standing on some type of contraption on the road], 16
    - [Carousel number 16 [Europe; commercially purchased slides of Europe]: Lowell Thomas and Frances Ryan Thomas sitting on couch], 17
    - [Carousel number 16 [Europe; commercially purchased slides of Europe]: Parking lot], 18
    - [Carousel number 16 [Europe; commercially purchased slides of Europe]: Road, city ahead], 19
    - [Carousel number 16 [Europe; commercially purchased slides of Europe]: Lowell Thomas leaning against bench in front of castle], 20
  - Carousel number 16 [Europe; commercially purchased slides of Europe], circa 1972; 7 (Box 1586)
    - [Carousel number 16 [Europe; commercially purchased slides of Europe]: Inside of an airport], 1
    - [Carousel number 16 [Europe; commercially purchased slides of Europe]: Lowell Thomas, Frances Ryan Thomas, a man, and a woman sitting inside airport], 2
    - [Carousel number 16 [Europe; commercially purchased slides of Europe]: Street [signs for Cork and Limerick, Ireland?], 3
    - [Carousel number 16 [Europe; commercially purchased slides of Europe]: A building (hotel?) in Europe], 4
    - [Carousel number 16 [Europe; commercially purchased slides of Europe]: Lowell Thomas standing by fence, statue of Mary behind him], 5
    - [Carousel number 16 [Europe; commercially purchased slides of Europe]: An illegible sign], 6
    - [Carousel number 16 [Europe; commercially purchased slides of Europe]: Ruins in Europe (Ireland?)], 7
    - [Carousel number 16 [Europe; commercially purchased slides of Europe]: Frances Ryan Thomas sitting in car], 8
    - [Carousel number 16 [Europe; commercially purchased slides of Europe]: Lowell Thomas sitting on stone wall], 9
    - [Carousel number 16 [Europe; commercially purchased slides of Europe]: Lowell Thomas standing in front of cherry tree], 10
    - [Carousel number 16 [Europe; commercially purchased slides of Europe]: Lowell Thomas standing in front of statue at a park], 11
    - [Carousel number 16 [Europe; commercially purchased slides of Europe]: Lowell Thomas standing in a park in Europe], 12